Now we're actually pulling into the White House.
Walking down to the bowling alley.
There's one photo of me up here, and there's like literally like a sniper like right behind me in the photo.
That red hat.
Oh yeah, there we go.
Alright guys, I'm here with Donnie.
We are heading over to the White House right now for Easter.
Ready?
Let's go.
Let's see that new haircut, Donnie.
We gotta get it lower.
It's too puffy.
Alright, see you guys soon.
We're on the plane right now.
Look, what's the gunshot?
I'm on the plane.
I got the board so...
I'm just standing.
I got the...
Okay, we landed in D.C. Where's Spencer?
And now we are driving to the White House.
Now we're actually pulling into the White House.
Now we're at the White House.
Gotta go to Aroo's.
Me and Donnie are going to see the Washington Monument, which is the Lincoln Monument, and then the Memorial
Monument.
So that's where we're going to go.
Right, Donny?
Yeah.
It's a hard one to say.
So that the Langer Memorial and that the Washington Monument.
And me and Donnie are right now going to see both because we wanted to like get out and explore it.
I've been here years.
I haven't been here in years.
I mean, besides the inauguration.
Look how cool it is.
What do you think, Donnie?
Cool, pretty cool.
I want to climb it.
You want to climb it?
Yeah.
I think you can climb.
You want to go and try?
Yeah, let's go and try.
Look how cool it is.
Are you reading it?
You are running in my face.
I don't know what to do.
Should we stay away from the service?
Yeah, I think we should stay away from the service.
Does he see us?
We are trying to stay away from the service.
There, he got us.
He got us.
Donnie's hungry, even though we just ate a turkey, literally a turkey feast in the White House.
And Donnie's still hungry.
You got a canes in here?
Yeah.
You know what's really good is kava.
Do they have a kava here?
Donnie, should we rent some bikes?
Do you want to go rent some bikes?
We're walking right now to the monument.
I feel like we're on the wrong side.
Me and Donnie right now are running into the monument.
We've got the secret service behind us, and we're just running.
Oh my god, Donnie, I just did it.
I did not see her.
We almost there.
We're still running.
Georgia, Massachusetts, South
Carolina, Virginia, North Carolina, Vermont.
Where's the New York City one?
Tennessee, Louisiana, Mississippi, Alabama,
Missouri, Michigan, Texas.
Honestly, the run was worth it.
I'm literally sweating right now.
This is so cool.
So this is World War II Memorial, and it's really cool.
It's honestly, it's so crazy like the history, like when you come here, like architecture and the history, it's amazing.
We made it.
Donnie wants food now, right Donnie?
Now we're back at the warehouse.
Trying to find everyone.
I'm too tired of going to the movie theater room.
I'm exhausted.
I'm out of a good bed.
Are the stairs all turned around?
No.
Who's going to win?
Oh look, he got a great hat.
I love that red hat.
One, two.
Go, go, go, go.
I love the mustache.
Lonnie, what are your thoughts on this?
On your mark.
Get set...
T-Money is in.
Tristan, you know the eggs that they gave?
I heard it's really good to eat.
The eggs that they gave, I heard it's really good to eat.
You should try it out.
Look how good that looks.
Oh, he's getting into a good lie.
Oh, the stance.
He's not playing around.
The stance.
On your marks...
Get set...
Oh my god, something's in work.
Now we're waiting for Grandpa to go to the Oval Office.
How's it going so far?
It's going well, a little bit.
Good job out there, guys.
Glad you got in there.
Grandpa, hit it.
Do the jump dance.
Oh yeah, there we go.
Oh yeah.
Alright guys, well I hope you guys enjoyed the vlog.
We're leaving to see right now.
Um, and flying back to Florida, but like and subscribe, and I hope you guys enjoyed it, and we'll see you guys for the next one.
So everyone say peace.
Peace.